catholiccompany.com 2019-05-07

# Privacy Policy | The Catholic Company

Thank you for visiting Catholic Company. Catholic Company follows a strict privacy policy that keeps your personal information safe. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. We are committed to protecting your privacy at Catholic Company. We will not collect any personal information from you that you do not volunteer, and we are the sole owner of all information collected on this site. We do not sell, share, or rent this information to others in any way that we have not mentioned in this statement.

Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

### Collection of Information

We collect personal information including your name, email, address, phone, and billing information for internal purposes, to fulfill your orders, and to mail you catalogs. We may also collect information that does not directly identify you, such as your IP address and you navigate our site in order to enhance your shopping experience. We use your contact information to provide you with products and services you request as well as for analytical and marketing purposes, such as:

  * confirming, sending, and tracking your order, subscription, or registration;
  * communicating with you about your order, subscription, or registration;
  * analyzing preferences, trends, and statistics;
  * informing you of our new products, services, and offers;
  * providing you with other information about Catholic Company including personalized marketing communications.

We contact you only in ways compatible with your communications choices. To the extent necessary for such purposes, we take reasonable steps to ensure your contact information is accurate, complete, current, and otherwise reliable.

### Cookies / Tracking Technology

Catholic Company may use cookies and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookies and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to Catholic Company, and understanding how visitors use this site. Cookies also help us improve your experience and display more prominently goods and services that might interest you. Additionally, cookies are used to match a particular browsing session with their shopping cart, digital subscriptions, and other services we provide through our site. If you do not have cookies enabled, many features of our site may not work properly. We do not collect any personally identifiable information through these cookies. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service when you visit our web site and other web sites of interest to you. We also use cookies to remind us of who you are, tailor our products, services and advertising to suit the personal interests of you and others, estimate our audience size, assist our online merchants to track visits to and sales at our web sites and to process your order, track your status in our promotions, contests, and/or analyze your visiting patterns. Certain of our Service Providers may use cookies and collect information on our behalf. They are prohibited by our contract with them from sharing that information with anyone other than us or our other Service Providers.

### Distribution of Information

We do not share your email address with anyone. We may, on limited occasion, share your name, mailing address, and general shopping behavior with other responsible businesses we believe may offer products or services of interest to our customers. We might rent, exchange, share and/or cross-reference information, including contact information about you that will enable such persons or entities to contact you regarding products and services that may be of interest to you. To serve you better, we may combine information you give us online or through our catalogs. We may also combine that information with publicly available information and information we receive from or cross-reference with third parties and others, including providers of third party cookie and other third party browsing and use data. We use that combined information to enhance and personalize the shopping experience of you and others with us, and to recognize our customers so that we can communicate with you directly about our products and events that may be of interest to you, and for other promotional purposes. If you would like to remove your name from our shareable list please contact us.

### Third Parties / Partners

Catholic Company uses third-party web beacons to help analyze where visitors go and what they do while visiting our website. We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain information when you visit our web sites. These companies may use information collected during your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of interest to you. These companies may also tie identifiers associated with a particular browser or device to identifiers associated with other browsers or devices used by the same user or household in order to measure and target advertisements tailored to user interests across their devices and to send personalized marketing communications. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. Our web sites may contain links to web sites operated and maintained by third parties, over which we have no control. Privacy policies on such linked web sites may be different from our privacy policy.

### Security

We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect the confidentiality and security of information transmitted to us. While we strive to protect your contact information, to the extent permitted by law, we do not guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to or from our web sites, and you do so at your own risk. We urge you to keep any password that you establish with us in a safe place and not to divulge it to anyone. Also remember to log off your account and close your browser window when you have finished your visit. This is to ensure that others cannot access your account, especially if you are sharing a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place.

We never expose sensitive credit card data through the checkout process or through account management. All payment data submitted to us is encrypted. In order to minimize our customersâ€™ risk of fraud, we do not store credit card data. Once credit card information has been approved by our payment provider, we discard the data and process payment solely on the basis of the authorization information through our provider.

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy anytime. Any changes to this policy will be posted. Our Privacy Policy was updated on May 24, 2018.
